<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="shameQ1">After realizing you have received too much change at a store,
        you decide to keep it because the salesclerk doesn\'t notice. What is the likelihood
        that you would feel uncomfortable about keeping the money?</string>

    <string name="shameQ2">You are privately informed that you are the only one in your group that did not
make the honor society because you skipped too many days of school. What is the likelihood
that this would lead you to become more responsible about attending school?  </string>

    <string name="shameQ3">You rip an article out of a journal in the library and take it with you. Your teacher
discovers what you did and tells the librarian and your entire class. What is the likelihood that
this would make you would feel like a bad person?  </string>

    <string name="shameQ4">After making a big mistake on an important project at work in which people were
depending on you, your boss criticizes you in front of your coworkers. What is the likelihood
that you would feign sickness and leave work?</string>

    <string name="shameQ5">You reveal a friend’s secret, though your friend never finds out. What is the
likelihood that your failure to keep the secret would lead you to exert extra effort to keep
secrets in the future?</string>

    <string name="shameQ6">You give a bad presentation at work. Afterwards your boss tells your coworkers it
was your fault that your company lost the contract. What is the likelihood that you would feel
incompetent?  </string>

    <string name="shameQ7">A friend tells you that you boast a great deal. What is the likelihood that you would
stop spending time with that friend?  </string>

    <string name="shameQ8">Your home is very messy and unexpected guests knock on your door and invite
themselves in. What is the likelihood that you would avoid the guests until they leave? </string>

    <string name="shameQ9">You secretly commit a felony. What is the likelihood that you would feel remorse
about breaking the law?</string>

    <string name="shameQ10">You successfully exaggerate your damages in a lawsuit. Months later, your lies are
discovered and you are charged with perjury. What is the likelihood that you would think you
are a despicable human being?  </string>

    <string name="shameQ11">You strongly defend a point of view in a discussion, and though nobody was aware
of it, you realize that you were wrong. What is the likelihood that this would make you think
more carefully before you speak?  </string>

    <string name="shameQ12">You take office supplies home for personal use and are caught by your boss. What
is the likelihood that this would lead you to quit your job?</string>

    <string name="shameQ13">You make a mistake at work and find out a coworker is blamed for the error. Later,
your coworker confronts you about your mistake. What is the likelihood that you would feel
like a coward?  </string>

    <string name="shameQ14">At a coworker’s housewarming party, you spill red wine on their new cream‐colored carpet.
        You cover the stain with a chair so that nobody notices your mess. What is the
likelihood that you would feel that the way you acted was pathetic?</string>

    <string name="shameQ15">While discussing a heated subject with friends, you suddenly realize you are
shouting though nobody seems to notice. What is the likelihood that you would try to act more
considerately toward your friends?</string>

    <string name="shameQ16">You lie to people but they never find out about it. What is the likelihood that you
would feel terrible about the lies you told?</string>


<string name="shame_title">The GASP Scale</string>
    <string name="shame_desc">A new measure of guilt and shame proneness.
        Guilt and Shame Proness (GASP) scale measures individual differences in the propensity to
        experience guilt and shame across a range of personal transgressions.
    </string>
<string name="shame_source">Cohen, T. R., Wolf, S. T., Panter, A. T., and Insko, C. A. (2011).
    Introducing the GASP scale: A new measure of guilt and shame proneness. Journal of Personality
    and Social Psychology, 5, 947-966. doi:10.1037/a0022641</string>

</resources>